You have to be the remover of the force by letting flow happen.
Letting flow happen requires you even knowing you.
It's taken me so long to do so much self-work and self-exploration about what are the things that I allow to be force in my way.
Whether it's my codependency or abandonment issues or, you know, insecurities.
Like, what are the things that I am allowing to be in the way of me feeling good about my gut?
See, that's the thing.
It's not just to say, what am I allowing to get in the way of me getting to where I want to go?
That's not what I'm saying.
What am I allowing to get in the way of me trusting my gut?
Because when you know you have these things floating around, it makes you say, like, I don't know how much I can really listen to me.
Because you know you have these things.
Those things are force.
The jealousy, the codependency, the projecting, all of these things.